Hi everyone.
Thank you, thank you.
It's great to have you here today.
Today, I am going to talk about three things.
That's it.
We will start with why it's so important to us to have a product that we can make freely available and broadly available to everyone.
And we're always trying to find out ways to reduce friction.
So everyone can use ChatGPT wherever they're.
So today, we'll be releasing the desktop version of ChatGPT and the refreshed UI, that makes it simpler to use much more natural as well.
But the big news today is that we're launching our new flagship model.
And we're calling it GPT-4o.
The special thing about GPT-4o is that it brings GPT-4 level intelligence to everyone including our free users.
We'll be showing some live demos today to show the full extent of the capabilities of our new model.
And we'll be rolling them out iteratively over the next few weeks.
All right. So let's get started.
A very important part of our mission is to be able to make our advanced AI tools available to everyone for free.
We think it's very, very important that people have an intuitive feel for what the technology can do.
And so we really want to pair it with this broader understanding.
And we're always finding ways to reduce the friction and recently, we made ChatGPT available without the sign-up flow.
And today, we're also bringing the desktop app to ChatGPT, because we want you to be able to use it wherever you're.
As you can see it's easy, it's simple, it integrates very, very easily in your workflow.
Along with it, we have also refreshed the UI.
We note that these models get more and more complex.
But we want the experience of interaction to actually become more natural, easy, and for you not to focus on the UI at all but just focus on the collaboration with ChatGPT.
And now the big news.
Today, we're releasing our newest flagship model, this is GPT-4o.
GPT-4o provides GPT-4 level intelligence, but it is much faster.
And it improves on its capabilities across text, vision, and audio.
For the past couple of years, we've been very focused on improving the intelligence of these models.
And they've gotten pretty good.
But this is the first time that we're really making a huge step forward when it comes to the ease of use.
And this is incredibly important, because we're looking at the future of interaction between ourselves and the machines.
And we think that GPT-4o is really shifting that paradigm into the future of collaboration, where this interaction becomes much more natural and far, far easier.
But you know, making this happen is actually quite complex, because when we interact with one another there's a lot of stuff that we take for granted.
You know the ease of our dialog when we interrupt one another, the background noises, the multiple voices in a conversation, or, you know, understanding the tone of voice.
All of these things are actually quite complex for, for these models.
And until now, with voice mode, we had three models that come together to deliver this experience.
We have transcription, intelligence, and then text to speech.
All comes together in orchestration to deliver voice mode.
This also brings a lot of latency to the experience, and it really breaks that immersion in the collaboration with ChatGPT.
But now, with GPT-4o, this all happens natively.
GPT-4o reasons across voice, text, and vision.
And with these incredible efficiencies, it also allows us to bring the GPT-4o class intelligence to our free users.
This is something that we've been trying to do for many, many months.
And we're very, very excited to finally bring GPT-4o to all of our users.